A Guide to the Henry G. Kunkel papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA273
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Reprints, 1943-1984; 8
  - Annotated Reprints by Others, 8.2
    - "Immunoglobulins and Crossed Immunoelectrophoresis": Anders 0. Grubb, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - "Immunological Facilitation, a Broadening of the Concept of the Enhancement Phenomenon": G.A. Voisin, 1971 (Box 108, Folder 26)
    - "The Immunopathology of Joint Inflammation in Rheumatoid Arthritis": Nathan J. Zvaifler, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - "Interactions Between Staphylococcal Protein A andy Globulins": Giiran Kronval, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - "Les Antiglobulines Individuelles": J. Dausset, J. Colombani, and M. Colombani, 1962 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - "Les Groupes des Gamma - Globulines Chez L'Homme": Dr. J. Brocteur, 1962 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - "Localization of Gm Markers to Different Molecular Regions of the Fe Fragment": J.B. Natvig and M.W. Turner, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Lymphocytes and Leukemia, 1976-1977, undated (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - "Medical Science, The Clinical Trial and Society": Robert Q. Marston, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - "A Method for Increasing the Sensitivity of Radial-Immunodiffusion Assay": Elliot Alpert, Margaret Momoe, and Peter H. Schur, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - "The MHC -related Antigen Receptor on T Cells. I. Isolation with a Monoclonal Antibody": Kathryn Haskins, Ralph Kubo, et al., 1983 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Misc. Human Systems, 1979-1981 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Mixed Agglutination -Reprints and Talk, 1956-1966 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - "Morbus Lympholyticus Congenitalis" (includes supplements): Alfons F. Lambrechts and Jules J. Snoijink, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - "Natural Killer Cells in Systemic Lupus Erythematosus": Marianne L. Egan, Steven L. Mendelsohn, et al., 1983 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - "On Cold Agglutinin Syndrome - Biochemistry and Physiology of Cold Agglutinins, Thermodynamics of Cold Agglutinin Reactions": Henrik Olesen, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - "P 15, A Nuclear -associated Protein of Human Sperm. Identification of Four Variants and their Occurrence in Normal and Abnormal Seminal Cells", undated (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - "Para1ymphomatous Disease - The Syndrome ofMacrog1obulinemia": Stephan E. Ritzmann, Jerry C. Daniels, and William C. Levin, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - 17 "Pepsin Digestion of Human G -Myeloma Proteins of Different Subclasses": M.W. Turner, H.H. Bennich, and J.B. Natvig, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Polyribonucleotides, 1964-1968 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - "Primary Structure and EVolution of Cytochrome C": E. Margoliash, 1963 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - "Proceedings -Immunologic Disease": Sidney Raffel, 1958 (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - "The Production of Antisera to Human yG Subclasses in Rabbits Using Immunological Unresponsiveness": H.L. Spiegelberg, and W.O. Weigle, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Reprints and Articles, 1982-1983 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Reprints by Others from The Rockefeller University, 1979, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Review of the Notation tor the Allotypic and Related Markers of Human Immunoglobulins, includes a note from Stephen Litwin, undated (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Rheum. Factors, 1951-1962 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Rheum. Factors, 1951-1962 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Rx of Proteins? - Reprints and Talk, 1947-1967 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - "Simon Flexner, 1863 -1946": Peyton Rous, 1949 November (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - "Site of J Chain Attachment to Human Polymeric IgA": Jiri Mestecky, Ralph E. Schrohenloher, et al., 1974 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - "The Specificity of Antigenic Recognition of Antibody Heavy Chain": E. Haber and F.F. Richards, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - "Studies on the Chemistry of Blood Coagulation. XII. An Electrophoretic Study of the Effect of Anti-coagulants on Human Plasma Proteins, with Remarks on the Separation of the Heparin Complement": Erwin Chargraff, Morris Ziff, and Dan H. Moore, 1941 May (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - "Studies on the Gamma Globulin (Gm) Serum Groups": Morten Harboe, 1961 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - "Studies on Human Secretory Immunoglobulins. Gross Conformations of Secretory IgA and Binding of Secretory Component to Immunoglobulins A and M": Erik Lindh, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - "Studies of Selective Deficiency of Serum IgA and its Significance in Blood Transfusion": Jukka Koistinen, 1975 November (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Studies in the Specificities of yG-Globulin and Anti-y-Globulin Factors in Human Sera": Jacob B. Natvig, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - T Cells, 1974-1980, undated (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Teodorescu, Marius, 1975-1980 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - "Terminal Deoxynucleotidyl Transferase in the Diagnosis of Leukemia and Malignant Lymphoma": Patrick C. Kung, et al., 1978 May (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - "Tumor-Specific Antigen of Murine T-Lymphoma Defined with Monoclonal Antibody": James P. Allison, Bradley W. Mcintyre, and David Bloch, 1982 November (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - "Variations in the S -S Bridges of Immunoglobulins G -Interchain Disulphide Bridges of yG3 Myeloma Proteins": B. Frangione and C. Milstein, 1968 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Zoltan Ovary, 1958-1959 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Zuck. - Doh. Phenomenon, 1977, undated (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Ephemera, 1948-1978; 9
  The collection is open for scholarly research with select materials restricted, as noted in the accompanying PDF.
  Special arrangements may be required in order to view materials. Individual items may be restricted at the discretion of RAC.
  - Stamps, 1960-1963 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #1, undated (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #1 - related negatives, undated (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #2, undated (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #3, undated (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #4, undated (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #5, undated (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #6, undated (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #7, undated (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #8, undated (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #8, undated (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #9, undated (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #10, undated (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #11, undated (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #12, undated (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #13, undated (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #14, undated (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #15, undated (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #15 - related photos, undated (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #16, undated (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #17, undated (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #18, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - Electrophoresis Gel # 19, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #20, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 23)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #21, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #22, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #23, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 26)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #24, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #25, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #25-related photos, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #26, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #26- related photos, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #27, undated (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #28, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #28-related photos, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #29, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #30, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #30, undated (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #30-related photos, undated (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #31, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #32, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #33, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #33- related photos, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #34, undated (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #35, undated (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #36, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #37, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #38, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #39, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #40, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #41, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #42, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #43, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #44, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #45, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #46, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #47, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #48, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #49, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #50, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #51, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #52, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #54, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #55, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #56, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #57, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #58, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #59, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #60, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #61, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Electrophoresis Gel #62, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Unlabeled Electrophoresis Gels (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Big Daddy Button (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Oversized chart (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Audio tape -Dr Levine Lecture, Dr. Kunkel Introduction: RU, 1979 April 3 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Graphic Services: photograph, slides, and negatives (Box 118)
    - HE: 95-7, 1948 January 21 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - 62-1379: James C. Allen, 1962 October 1 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - 61-1091, 1961 July (Box 118, Folder 3)
      Restricted from scholarly research.
    - 7168-7: Comparisons Between the Specific Activity ofVarious Hemoglobin Fractions at Different Times after Administration of Fe59, 1957 April 1 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - 9907-7 A&B: Agar Plates, 1959 October 15 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - 60-532: Copy Mtd. Print, 1960 April 27 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - 62-356 actually 62-1043 A &B: Copy Charts, 1962 August 15 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - 62-948: Petri Dish, 1962 June 19 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - 62-1226: Copy Gels, 1962 November 9 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - 62-971: Petri Dish, 1962 June 22 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - 62-1246 A-E: Petri Dishes, 1962 September 4 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - 62-1431, 1962 October 18 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - 62-1449 A-C: Copy Page Proof from Waverly Press, Inc. book, 1962 October 25 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - 62-1460: Typed Chart, 1962 October 25 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - 78 A&B: Chart, 1948 January 9 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - 92-7: HE (Jones), 1948 January 21 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - 93-7:HE(Jones), 1948 January 21 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - 94-7: HE (Babcock), 1948 January 21 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - 60-989: Copy mtd. Print, 1960 August 24 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - 60-926: Copy Typed Tables, 1960 August 10 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - 60-671: Chart, 1960 May 26 (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - 60-1138: Photo Plates, 1960 October 19 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - 62-1229 A-C: Copy Slides, 1962 August 27 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - 60-1144: Agar Plates, 1960 October 13 (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - 60-1186: Agar Plates, 1960 October 27 (Box 118, Folder 25)
    - 60-1274: Copy Glass Plates, 1960 November 28 (Box 118, Folder 26)
    - 60-1365: Copy Glass Plates, 1960 December 19 (Box 118, Folder 27)
    - 61-130: Copy Pedigree, 1963 March 27 (Box 118, Folder 28)
    - 61-732: Copy Tables, 1961 May 16 (Box 118, Folder 29)
    - 61-1204 A-I: Copy Charts, 1961 August 15 (Box 118, Folder 30)
    - 61-1526: Chart, 1961 November 16 (Box 118, Folder 31)
    - 62-37 A&B: Petri Dishes, 1962 September 18 (Box 118, Folder 32)
    - 62-85 A-C: Plates and Slide, 1962 April 2 (Box 118, Folder 33)
    - 62-90 A-D: Petri Dishes, 1962 January 25 (Box 118, Folder 34)
    - 62-143: Starch Gel, 1962 January 29 (Box 118, Folder 35)
    - 62-152 A-D, 1962 February 1 (Box 118, Folder 36)
    - 62-184, 1962 February 6 (Box 118, Folder 37)
    - 62-207 A&B: Petri Dishes, 1962 February 15 (Box 118, Folder 38)
    - 62-228: Petri Dish, 1962 April12 (Box 118, Folder 39)
    - 8891-7: Petri Dish, 1959 January 9 (Box 118, Folder 40)
    - 8893-7, 1959 January 26 (Box 118, Folder 41)
    - 8900-7 A&B: Typed Charts, 1960 July 7 (Box 118, Folder 42)
    - 8953-7:0uchterlony Plate VI, 1959 January 28 (Box 118, Folder 43)
    - 8959-7 A&B: Agar Plates, 1959 January 28 (Box 118, Folder 44)
    - 9053-7: Chart, 1959 February 25 (Box 118, Folder 45)
    - 9068-7: Line Drawing, 1959 March 3 (Box 118, Folder 46)
    - 9096-7 A&B: Typed Table and Chart, 1959 April 7 (Box 118, Folder 47)
    - 9154-7 A&B: Line Drawings (Pedigree), 1959 March 18 (Box 118, Folder 48)
    - 9988-7 A&B: Chart and C.T., 1960 July 7 (Box 118, Folder 49)
    - 993-7: Typed Chart, 1970 July 7 (Box 118, Folder 50)
    - 10026-7 A&B: Petri Dishes, 1959 November 17 (Box 118, Folder 51)
    - 10029-7: Serum, 1959 November 13 (Box 118, Folder 52)
    - 10049-7:Agar Plate, 1959 November 20 (Box 118, Folder 53)
    - 10064-7 A-E: C.T. Mounted HB for L.S., 1960 July 26 (Box 118, Folder 54)
    - 10079-7: Typed Table, 1959 November 30 (Box 118, Folder 55)
    - 10142-7: Copy Chart, 1960 July 7 (Box 118, Folder 56)
    - 10143-7: Copy Negs., 1959 December 31 (Box 118, Folder 57)
    - 60-163 A-C: Copy Prints, 1961 February 3 (Box 118, Folder 58)
    - 60-263: Copy Chart, 1961 February 3 (Box 118, Folder 59)
    - 60-485: Copy Chart, 1960 July 6 (Box 118, Folder 60)
    - 60-492 A-D: Copy Charts, 1960 July 15 (Box 118, Folder 61)
    - 61-558: Copy Chart, 1960 May 2 (Box 118, Folder 62)
    - 60-651: Copy Typed Table, 1960 May 19 (Box 118, Folder 63)
    - 60-644: Copy Slides, 1960 June 1 (Box 118, Folder 64)
    - 9865-7: Petri Dish, 1959 September 30 (Box 118, Folder 65)
    - 9938-7 A&B: Petri Dishes, 1959 November 13 (Box 118, Folder 66)
    - E.C. Franklin (Box 118, Folder 67)
    - 62-261: Fig. 2-B (color), 1962 February 27 (Box 118, Folder 68)
    - Negatives: Petri Dishes, 1969 May (Box 118, Folder 69)
    - Negative: Petri Dish (Box 118, Folder 70)
    - Negatives, 1967 January 10 (Box 118, Folder 71)
    - Chart, 1969 September 22 (Box 118, Folder 72)
    - Negative, 1969 September 22 (Box 118, Folder 73)
    - Negative, 1969 March 21 (Box 118, Folder 74)
    - Petri Dishes, 1968 December 10 (Box 118, Folder 75)
    - Negatives: Slides for Washington Talk, 1968 October 28 (Box 118, Folder 76)
    - Negatives, 1967 October 30 (Box 118, Folder 77)
    - Negative, 1967 May 22 (Box 118, Folder 78)
    - Negatives, 1968 July 24 (Box 118, Folder 79)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 80)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 81)
    - Negatives: Petri Dishes (Box 118, Folder 82)
    - Negative: 3006 (Box 118, Folder 83)
    - Negative (Box 118, Folder 84)
    - Negative, 1971 February (Box 118, Folder 85)
    - Negative: NY Academy Meeting (Immunoglobulin Conference), 1971 March 5 (Box 118, Folder 86)
    - Negatives: 1967 (Box 118, Folder 87)
    - Negatives: Petri Dishes, 1968 AprilS (Box 118, Folder 88)
    - Negative: Chart, 1968 September 24 (Box 118, Folder 89)
    - Negative: Boxes with Arrows, 1968 October 4 (Box 118, Folder 90)
    - Negatives, 1968 April 16 (Box 118, Folder 91)
    - Negatives, 1968 January 12 (Box 118, Folder 92)
    - Negative: NY Heart Association, 1971 February (Box 118, Folder 93)
    - Negative: So. Florida Meeting, 1971 February 4 (Box 118, Folder 94)
    - Negatives: Dallas and Galveston, 1971 February (Box 118, Folder 95)
    - Prints: Complement Workshop, Washington, 1971 January (Box 118, Folder 96)
    - Negatives: Plates, 1972 January 19 (Box 118, Folder 97)
    - Negatives: Slides for Albuquerque, 1972 January 19 (Box 118, Folder 98)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 99)
    - Negatives: Talk in Washington, D.C., 1968 October 28 -31 (Box 118, Folder 100)
    - Negatives, 1971 November 9 (Box 118, Folder 101)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 102)
    - Negatives: Jacob B. Natvig: Family Slides, 1967 November (Box 118, Folder 103)
    - Negative: 3230 (Box 118, Folder 104)
    - Negative (Box 118, Folder 105)
    - Negative: Black and White (Box 118, Folder 106)
    - Negative (Box 118, Folder 107)
    - Negative: 5 Slides, 1971 October 21 (Box 118, Folder 108)
    - Negatives: Buffalo Meeting, 1971 May 11 (Box 118, Folder 109)
    - Negative: Chart (Box 118, Folder 110)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 111)
    - Negatives: Petri Dishes: Ruth-Plates (Box 118, Folder 112)
    - Negatives, 1969 September 15 (Box 118, Folder 113)
    - Negative, 1969 September 23 (Box 118, Folder 114)
    - Negatives, 1970 April28 (Box 118, Folder 115)
    - Negative, 1970 May8 (Box 118, Folder 116)
    - Negative, 1970 June 1 (Box 118, Folder 117)
    - Negatives: 2 Plates, 1970 (Box 118, Folder 118)
    - Negatives, 1970 September (Box 118, Folder 119)
    - Negative, 1970 September (Box 118, Folder 120)
    - Negatives, 1970 September (Box 118, Folder 121)
    - Negative: Petri Dish, 1969 October 21 (Box 118, Folder 122)
    - Negative: 1323, 1970 (Box 118, Folder 123)
    - Negatives: 1323 and Chart, September 1970 (Box 118, Folder 124)
    - Dr. Natvig Negatives, 1967 May 24 (Box 118, Folder 125)
    - Negative, 1967 April24 (Box 118, Folder 126)
    - Negative, 1967 April27 (Box 118, Folder 127)
    - Negative, 1967 May 12 (Box 118, Folder 128)
    - Prints and Negatives, 1967 September 7 (Box 118, Folder 129)
    - Negative, 1967 May 5 (Box 118, Folder 130)
    - Negatives: 66-2195, 1966 June21 (Box 118, Folder 131)
    - Prints: Figures-Bearn and Kunkel: 65-3226 (Box 118, Folder 132)
    - Negative: Chart (Box 118, Folder 133)
    - Negative: Chart (Box 118, Folder 134)
    - Negative: 66-2170 (Box 118, Folder 135)
    - Negative, 1967 March 24 (Box 118, Folder 136)
    - Negative (Box 118, Folder 137)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 138)
    - Negatives, 1965 March 29 (Box 118, Folder 139)
    - Negative: 65-3535 (Box 118, Folder 140)
    - Negatives, 1966 October 26 (Box 118, Folder 141)
    - Negatives: 65-1936, 1965 May 27 (Box 118, Folder 142)
    - Negative: 63-0268, 1963 January 30 (Box 118, Folder 143)
    - Negative: 63-0585, 1963 February 20 (Box 118, Folder 144)
    - Negative: 63-2183, 1963 August 2 (Box 118, Folder 145)
    - Negatives: 63-1811 A&B, 1963 June 26 (Box 118, Folder 146)
    - Negative: 63-2166, 1963 August 2 (Box 118, Folder 147)
    - Negative: 63-1659, 1963 July 2 (Box 118, Folder 148)
    - Negative: Plate: 63-1690, 1963 June 25 (Box 118, Folder 149)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 150)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 151)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 152)
    - Negative: 67-1417, 1967 April 17 (Box 118, Folder 153)
    - Negative:, 1967 April 26 (Box 118, Folder 154)
    - Negative: 67-1644, 1967 May 2 (Box 118, Folder 155)
    - Negatives: 67-1357 4890-4896, 1967 May 17 (Box 118, Folder 156)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 157)
    - Negative: 65-2132, 1965 June 22 (Box 118, Folder 158)
    - Negative: 65-2305, 1965 June 18 (Box 118, Folder 159)
    - Negative: 65-3070, 1965 September 15 (Box 118, Folder 160)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 161)
    - Negative: 65-1989: May 27 (Box 118, Folder 162)
    - Negative: Plate: 65-1385, 1965 April 22 (Box 118, Folder 163)
    - Negative: 65-789 (Box 118, Folder 164)
    - Negative (Box 118, Folder 165)
    - Negative, 1965 July 13 (Box 118, Folder 166)
    - Print: Portrait of Dr. Meltzer (Box 118, Folder 167)
    - Negatives: Charts, 1966 December 13 (Box 118, Folder 168)
    - Negative:, 1967 January 12 (Box 118, Folder 169)
    - Negative: 65-1270, 1965 April12 (Box 118, Folder 170)
    - Negatives, 1966 December 8 (Box 118, Folder 171)
    - Negative, 1967 January 12 (Box 118, Folder 172)
    - Negative: 65-383, 1965 February 10 (Box 118, Folder 173)
    - Negatives: Plates: 65-1361, 1965 April22 (Box 118, Folder 174)
    - Negative: 66-1195, 1966 April 6 (Box 118, Folder 175)
    - Negatives: Plates: 65-1546, April 30 (Box 118, Folder 176)
    - Prints: Antibodies ag-4-glob. after..., 1965 June (Box 118, Folder 177)
    - Negative: 62-2228 (Box 118, Folder 178)
    - Negative: 63-3491, 1964 January 27 (Box 118, Folder 179)
    - Negative: 64-2186, July 23 (Box 118, Folder 180)
    - Negative (Box 118, Folder 181)
    - Negatives: Plates: 64-0923 A&B, 1964 March 30 (Box 118, Folder 182)
    - Negatives: 64-0947, 1964 March 31 (Box 118, Folder 183)
    - Negative: Plate: 64-6945, 1964 March 31 (Box 118, Folder 184)
    - Negative: 64-0623, 1964 March 5 (Box 118, Folder 185)
    - Negative: Plate: 64-0663, 1964 March 6 (Box 118, Folder 186)
    - Negative: Plate: 64-499, 1964 February 26 (Box 118, Folder 187)
    - Negative: 64-9356 (Box 118, Folder 188)
    - Negative: 64-0203, 1964 January 27 (Box 118, Folder 189)
    - Negatives: 64-0252, 1964 January 30 (Box 118, Folder 190)
    - Prints (Box 118, Folder 191)
    - Negative: 61-137, 1961 January 26 (Box 118, Folder 192)
    - Negative, 1966 August 17 (Box 118, Folder 193)
    - Negatives: 65-866 (Box 118, Folder 194)
    - Negative: 66-62 (Box 118, Folder 195)
    - Negative: 65-907, 1965 March 3, 17 (Box 118, Folder 196)
    - Negative: 65-412, 1965 February 10 (Box 118, Folder 197)
    - Negative: 556/557, 1965 March 15 (Box 118, Folder 198)
    - Negatives: 65-1494, 1965 April 23 (Box 118, Folder 199)
    - Negatives: 66-702, 1966 March 14 (Box 118, Folder 200)
    - Negative, 1966 February I (Box 118, Folder 201)
    - Negative: 66-920, 1966 March 28 (Box 118, Folder 202)
    - Negatives: 66-2125, 1965 June 20 (Box 118, Folder 203)
    - Negatives: 4293, 1967 February 10 (Box 118, Folder 204)
    - Negative: 66-1555 (Box 118, Folder 205)
    - Negative, 1963 January (Box 118, Folder 206)
    - Negative: 63-0131, 1963 January 18 (Box 118, Folder 207)
    - Negative: Plate: 63-0009, 1963 January 8 (Box 118, Folder 208)
    - Negative: 62-2302, 1962 December 27 (Box 118, Folder 209)
    - Negative: 62-2240 (Box 118, Folder 210)
    - Negative: 63-906, 1963 March 27 (Box 118, Folder 211)
    - Negative: 62-2266 (Box 118, Folder 212)
    - Negatives: 62-2301 A&B (Box 118, Folder 213)
    - Negative: Plate (Box 118, Folder 214)
    - Negatives: 64-1055, 1964 April 8 (Box 118, Folder 215)
    - Negatives: 62-2271 A&B (Box 118, Folder 216)
    - Negative: 64-0115 (Box 118, Folder 217)
    - Negative: 64-1788 (Box 118, Folder 218)
    - Negative: 64-2697, 1964 September21 (Box 118, Folder 219)
    - Negative: 64-0115, 1964 November 2 (Box 118, Folder 220)
    - Negatives: 64-2652, 1964 September 11 (Box 118, Folder 221)
    - Negative: 64-2680 (Box 118, Folder 222)
    - Negatives: 64-2635, 1964 September 16 (Box 118, Folder 223)
    - Negatives: 64-1587 (Box 118, Folder 224)
    - Negatives: 64-1532 (Box 118, Folder 225)
    - Negatives: 64-722:, 1964 May 12 (Box 118, Folder 226)
    - Negatives: 64-1229, 1964 April 15 (Box 118, Folder 227)
    - Negative: 64-1638, 1964 May 12 (Box 118, Folder 228)
    - Negative: 64-1765, 1964 May 26 (Box 118, Folder 229)
    - (Negative: 64-2107, 1964 July I (Box 118, Folder 230)
    - Negative: 64-2051 (Box 118, Folder 231)
    - Negatives: 64-2127, 1964 July 7 (Box 118, Folder 232)
    - Negative: 63-1186, 1963 April 22 (Box 118, Folder 233)
    - Negative: 63-1152, 1963 April 13 (Box 118, Folder 234)
    - Negative: 63-3545, 1964 January 8 (Box 118, Folder 235)
    - Negative: 63-3474, 1963 December 23 (Box 118, Folder 236)
    - Negatives: 63-3507 A-C, 1964 January 3 (Box 118, Folder 237)